welcome finally
to episode
four of the
Webdune Diaries in
season one, the
Fox Stevenson season.
Webdune is a
web agency,
so we,
develop, which is
coding, building websites,
on tools like
Webflow, WordPress,
Wix, Squarespace,
usually Webflow.
and we also
design them.
So there's a
tool called Figma
how do we
make money?
Usually, I'm
subcontracting for a
marketing agency or
a digital agency
or web agency.
how do I
get these jobs?
Usually through Unicorn
Factory. It's a
freelancer marketplace based,
in New Zealand,
good high-quality leads,
rather than the
Fiverr situation
of, you
know, race to
the bottom, I
want a website
for $5 situation.
and then from
Unicorn Factory,
I've got ongoing
relationships that I'll
keep working with
agencies or clients,
I'm working for
HNDRX. they're a
web agency from
Raglan. I'm doing
some work with,
Onsite Media, they're
a marketing digital
agency from Tauranga.
doing a
little bit of
work for Launch
Agency, they're a
big marketing agency,
from Hamilton.
And then
in terms of
direct clients, I'm
doing some work
for Legend Story.
a landing
page design.
And then a
little bit of
work with SellMyCell.
We just wrapped
up a massive
phase two new
website for them.
Constantly working with
Spirit of Douglas,
a cool plane,
so not-for-profit,
so next episode,
it would
be awesome to
show you guys
what I do
day to day.
portfolio, a bit
of a
showcase, maybe some
fancy swirling animations,